<resources>
    <string name="app_name">It\'s My Birthday</string>

    <string name="text1">Excelsior Thread Art</string>
    <string name="text2">6th Anniversary</string>
    <string name="text3">6th Anniversary</string>
    <string name="text4">6th Anniversary Cake</string>
    <string name="text5">6th Anniversary Party</string>
    <string name="text6">Excelsior Team</string>
    <string name="text7">Excelsior Team</string>
    <string name="text8">Birthday 2018</string>
    <string name="text9">Christmas 2018</string>
    <string name="text10">Rajal Birthday</string>
    <string name="text11">August Birthday</string>
    <string name="text12">Poojan Birthday</string>


    <string name="car_hint">Here I come and There I Go,I move really fast anywhere I go, That\'s why you take me when you are hurry, when I zoom by I might look bloory</string>

    <string name="tample_hint">Tample</string>
    <string name="stickey_note_hint">I\'m full of pins and intresting stuff, People stare and can\'t get enough paper and invites hang around up on the wall I can be found</string>
    <string name="moniter_hint">Keep me open keep me close, ther\'s really nothing I Oppose.But when it rains or when It\'s cold to keeep me shut is what you are told</string>
    <string name="projector_hint">Flat, black &amp; Seemingly boring,I sit in the office all day &amp; night. Not until you turn me on do colors flash</string>
    <string name="coofie_hint">You say we are pats, that we are best friends. But only until the morning ends. You say I give you fuel for the day and when we are done you are gone away</string>
    <string name="broadband_hint">it\'s all fun &amp; game until I start to spott when my blinking light go black then you\'ll start to--- . I help you get things done, you say but rarely that you touch me, only when the lights go out do you try to press me</string>
    <string name="register_hint">There\'s a place nearby you\'ll want to meet a portal place where people greet find me at the keppers home search me with a fine toothed comb</string>
    <string name="frize_hint">Open Me Up And Take a Peek,Inside You Will Find A Frozan Treat</string>
    <string name="Chair_hint">Chair</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="wish1">Anjali</string>
    <string name="wish2">Pooja</string>
    <string name="wish3">Hemins</string>
    <string name="wish4">Yogesh</string>
    <string name="wish5">Rajal</string>
    <string name="wish6">Shubhada</string>
    <string name="wish7">Abhilav</string>
    <string name="wish8">Vaishali</string>
    <string name="wish9">Shruti</string>
    <string name="wish10">Nikita</string>
    <string name="wish11">Nidhi</string>
    <string name="wish12">Dhrumil</string>
    <string name="wish13">Kena</string>
    <string name="wish14">Pratik</string>
    <string name="wish15">Ashish</string>
    <string name="wish16">JD</string>
    <string name="wish17">Komal</string>
    <string name="wish18">Himanshu</string>
    <string name="wish19">Parshva</string>
    <string name="wish20">Kishan</string>
    <string name="wish21">Satyam</string>
    <string name="wish22">Sikha</string>
    <string name="wish23">Tanuja</string>
    <string name="wish24">Darshan</string>
    <string name="wish25">Kanu Bhai</string>
    <string name="wish26">Prasoon</string>
    <string name="wish27">Mehul</string>


    <string name="wishD1">Happy birthday to a brother who has the worlds greatest sister. Dang you are so lucky!!</string>
    <string name="wishD2">Being a great leader that you are. You have surely guided us in every step of life. Thanks for your support and guidance sir it means a lot. Happy Birthday Kushal Sir stay blessed in life.  </string>
    <string name="wishD3">On my brothers birthday I am making a wish, that we always remain inseparable Like water and fish. Happy birthday Bro!!</string>
    <string name="wishD4">Everyday you sparkle but today you rule. A year older and still as awesome as ever! Appi Birthday.</string>
    <string name="wishD5">Happy Birthday!! Hope you have a great day today and the year ahead is full of many blessings.</string>
    <string name="wishD6">Wishing you a many many happy returns of the day sir. A person like you may be very less who have encouraged everyone in every situation. May your all wishes come true.Happy Birthday! </string>
    <string name="wishD7">Happy Birthday KP! You are the key to this success. May god keey you happy and healthy so that you can always lead us.</string>
    <string name="wishD8">Wishing a very happy birthday to a super cool boss. Work becomes much more fun with you around. Have a great day.</string>
    <string name="wishD9">You inspire and motivate me always. May all your hopes and dreams come true and your future be filled with happiness. HBD Kushal Sir!! </string>
    <string name="wishD10">May god complete all your wishes. Happy birthday Sir!</string>
    <string name="wishD11">Many many happy returns of the day!</string>
    <string name="wishD12">Your bday is the first day of another 365 day journey. Be the shining thread in the beautiful tapestry of the world to make this year the best ever. Enjoy the ride.</string>
    <string name="wishD13">Boss, may the years ahead be full of happiness and opportunities. Happy Birthday!</string>
    <string name="wishD14">Wishing you a very happy birthday sir. you have been a great guide. Your support and advice have helped shape my career. Thanks for being the best boss ever!!</string>
    <string name="wishD15">Today is a special day for the best leader in the world. You are responsible for all our progress and success. Without your help, we never would have reached where we are today. We are really lucky to work with you. Happy birthday sir!</string>
    <string name="wishD16">Your gentleness and sincerity have always inspired us. Another year has gone by. I m glad, i was a part of it. May this new year bring fatal happiness. Happy birthday sir!</string>
    <string name="wishD17">More and more get achievements in your life. Wish you very happy birthday sir.</string>
    <string name="wishD18">Hope your special day brings you all that your heart desire! Here is wishing you a day is full of pleasant surprise. Happy birthday Sir.</string>
    <string name="wishD19">May god bless every day of your life with a way of sun a touch of hope a glint of joy and a drop of love. Happy birthday.</string>
    <string name="wishD20">I feel proud when i call you my mentor. I want to feel this today and everyday. Happ Bday to most creative person. Happy birthday Sir..</string>
    <string name="wishD21">Wish you all the best in your life and always be happy. I dont know what to write more. Have to a bright healthy future. Simply or amazing boss take of your self. Thank You!</string>
    <string name="wishD22">On your special day, I wish you the greatest happiness That can be in this world! Happy birthday Jiju!!</string>
    <string name="wishD23">Wish you a very happy birthday kushal. I just wanna to say that you are such a nice and kind person. You are always ready to help your friends and family. I have learnt lots of things from you and always with your happiness and prosperity. Happy Birthday. Enjoy!!</string>
    <string name="wishD24">The one who leaves their comfort zone outlines just like you. Happy birthday sir. May god bless you!</string>
    <string name="wishD25">Wishing you a very happy birthday. May all your dreams come true.</string>
    <string name="wishD26">Wishing you a magical birthday filled with wonderful surprises.Happy birthday!</string>
    <string name="wishD27">I hope your special day brings you all the happiness you deserve in life.Happy Birthday!</string>

</resources>
