<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HBD-K</string>

    <string name="text1">Excelsior Thread Art</string>
    <string name="text2">6th Anniversary</string>
    <string name="text3">6th Anniversary</string>
    <string name="text4">6th Anniversary Cake</string>
    <string name="text5">6th Anniversary Party</string>
    <string name="text6">Excelsior Team</string>
    <string name="text7">Excelsior Team</string>
    <string name="text8">Birthday 2018</string>
    <string name="text9">Christmas 2018</string>
    <string name="text10">Rajal Birthday</string>
    <string name="text11">August Birthday</string>
    <string name="text12">Poojan Birthday</string>


    <string name="car_hint">Here I come and There I Go,I move really fast anywhere I go, That\'s why you take me when you are hurry, when I zoom by I might look bloory</string>
    <string name="barcode_hint">There will be a surprise for you, just scan it.</string>
    <string name="tample_hint">Tample</string>
    <string name="stickey_note_hint">I\'m full of pins and intresting stuff, People stare and can\'t get enough paper and invites hang around up on the wall I can be found</string>
    <string name="moniter_hint">Keep me open keep me close, ther\'s really nothing I Oppose.But when it rains or when It\'s cold to keeep me shut is what you are told</string>
    <string name="projector_hint">Flat, black &amp; Seemingly boring,I sit in the office all day &amp; night. Not until you turn me on do colors flash</string>
    <string name="coofie_hint">You say we are pats, that we are best friends. But only until the morning ends. You say I give you fuel for the day and when we are done you are gone away</string>
    <string name="broadband_hint">it\'s all fun &amp; game until I start to spott when my blinking light go black then you\'ll start to--- . I help you get things done, you say but rareky that you touch me, only when the lights go out do you try to press me</string>
    <string name="register_hint">There\'s a place nearby you\'ll want to meet a portal place where people greet find me at the keppers home search me with a fine toothed comb</string>
    <string name="frize_hint">Open Me Up And Take a Peek,Inside You Will Find A Frozan Treat</string>
    <string name="Chair_hint">Chair</string>

</resources>
