<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HBD-K</string>

    <string name="text1">Excelsior Thread Art</string>
    <string name="text2">6th Anniversary</string>
    <string name="text3">6th Anniversary</string>
    <string name="text4">6th Anniversary Cake</string>
    <string name="text5">6th Anniversary Party</string>
    <string name="text6">Excelsior Team</string>
    <string name="text7">Excelsior Team</string>
    <string name="text8">Birthday 2018</string>
    <string name="text9">Christmas 2018</string>
    <string name="text10">Rajal Birthday</string>
    <string name="text11">August Birthday</string>
    <string name="text12">Poojan Birthday</string>


    <string name="car_hint">Here I come and There I Go,I move really fast anywhere I go, That\'s why you take me when you are hurry, when I zoom by I might look bloory</string>

    <string name="tample_hint">Tample</string>
    <string name="stickey_note_hint">I\'m full of pins and intresting stuff, People stare and can\'t get enough paper and invites hang around up on the wall I can be found</string>
    <string name="moniter_hint">Keep me open keep me close, ther\'s really nothing I Oppose.But when it rains or when It\'s cold to keeep me shut is what you are told</string>
    <string name="projector_hint">Flat, black &amp; Seemingly boring,I sit in the office all day &amp; night. Not until you turn me on do colors flash</string>
    <string name="coofie_hint">You say we are pats, that we are best friends. But only until the morning ends. You say I give you fuel for the day and when we are done you are gone away</string>
    <string name="broadband_hint">it\'s all fun &amp; game until I start to spott when my blinking light go black then you\'ll start to--- . I help you get things done, you say but rareky that you touch me, only when the lights go out do you try to press me</string>
    <string name="register_hint">There\'s a place nearby you\'ll want to meet a portal place where people greet find me at the keppers home search me with a fine toothed comb</string>
    <string name="frize_hint">Open Me Up And Take a Peek,Inside You Will Find A Frozan Treat</string>
    <string name="Chair_hint">Chair</string>


    <string name="wish1">Anjali</string>
    <string name="wish2">Pooja</string>
    <string name="wish3">Hemins</string>
    <string name="wish4">Yogesh</string>
    <string name="wish5">Rajal</string>
    <string name="wish6">Shubhada</string>
    <string name="wish7">Abhilav</string>
    <string name="wish8">Vaishali</string>
    <string name="wish9">Shruti</string>
    <string name="wish10">Nikita</string>
    <string name="wish11">Nidhi</string>
    <string name="wish12">Dhrumil</string>
    <string name="wish13">Kena</string>
    <string name="wish14">Pratik</string>
    <string name="wish15">Ashish</string>
    <string name="wish16">JD</string>
    <string name="wish17">Komal</string>
    <string name="wish18">Himanshu</string>
    <string name="wish19">Parshva</string>
    <string name="wish20">Kishan</string>
    <string name="wish21">Satyam</string>
    <string name="wish22">Sikha</string>
    <string name="wish23">Tanuja</string>
    <string name="wish24">Darshan</string>
    <string name="wish25">Kanu Bhai</string>
    <string name="wish26">Prasoon</string>


    <string name="wishD1">Happy birthday to a brother who has the worlds greatest sister. Dang you are so lucky!!</string>
    <string name="wishD2">Being a great leader that you are. You have surely guided us in every step of life. Thanks for your support and guidance sir it means a lot. Happy Birthday Kushal Sir stay blessed in life.  </string>
    <string name="wishD3">On my brothers birthday I am making a wish, that we always remain inseparable Like water and fish. Happy birthday Bro!!</string>
    <string name="wishD4">Everyday you sparkle but today you rule. A year older and still as awesome as ever! Appi Birthday.</string>
    <string name="wishD5">Happy Birthday!! Hope you have a great day today and the year ahead is full of many blessings.</string>
    <string name="wishD6">Wishing you a many many happy returns of the day sir. A person like you may be very less who have encouraged everyone in every situation. May your all wishes come true.Happy Birthday! </string>
    <string name="wishD7">Happy Birthday KP! You are the key to this success. May god keey you happy and healthy so that you can always lead us.</string>
    <string name="wishD8">Wishing a very happy birthday to a super cool boss. Work becomes much more fun with you around. Have a great day.</string>
    <string name="wishD9">You inspire and motivate me always. May all your hopes and dreams come true and your future be filled with happiness. HBD Kushal Sir!! </string>
    <string name="wishD10">May god complete all your wishes. Happy birthday Sir!</string>
    <string name="wishD11">Many many happy returns of the day!</string>
    <string name="wishD12">Your bday is the first day of another 365 day journey. Be the shining thread in the beautiful tapestry of the world to make this year the best ever. Enjoy the ride.</string>
    <string name="wishD13">Boss, may the years ahead be full of happiness and opportunities. Happy Birthday!</string>
    <string name="wishD14">Wishing you a very happy birthday sir. you have been a great guide. Your support and advice have helped shape my career. Thanks for being the best boss ever!!</string>
    <string name="wishD15">Today is a special day for the best leader in the world. You are responsible for all our progress and success. Without your help, we never would have reached where we are today. We are really lucky to work with you. Happy birthday sir!</string>
    <string name="wishD16">Your gentleness and sincerity have always inspired us. Another year has gone by. I m glad, i was a part of it. May this new year bring fatal happiness. Happy birthday sir!</string>
    <string name="wishD17">More and more get achievements in your life. Wish you very happy birthday sir.</string>
    <string name="wishD18">Hope your special day brings you all that your heart desire! Here is wishing you a day is full of pleasant surprise. Happy birthday Sir.</string>
    <string name="wishD19">May god bless every day of your life with a way of sun a touch of hope a glint of joy and a drop of love. Happy birthday. જન્મ દિવસ ની ખુબ ખુબ શુભેચ્છા!!</string>
    <string name="wishD20">I feel proud when i call you my mentor. I want to feel this today and everyday. Happ Bday to most creative person. Happy birthday Sir..</string>
    <string name="wishD21">Wish you all the best in your life and always be happy. I dont know what to write more. Have to a bright healthy future. Simply or amazing boss take of your self. Thank You!</string>
    <string name="wishD22">On your special day, I wish you the greatest happiness That can be in this world! Happy birthday Jiju!!</string>
    <string name="wishD23"></string>
    <string name="wishD24">The one who leaves their comfort zone outlines just like you. Happy birthday sir. May god bless you!</string>
    <string name="wishD25">Wishing you a very happy birthday. May all your dreams come true.</string>
    <string name="wishD26">Wishing you a magical birthday filled with wonderful surprises.Happy birthday!</string>

</resources>
